<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Chondromalacie pately</title>
    <link>http://marketWO.github.io/hugo-start/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Chondromalacie pately</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>cs-cz</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 15:42:39 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://marketWO.github.io/hugo-start/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Chondromalaciace</title>
      <link>http://marketWO.github.io/hugo-start/post/chondromalaciace/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 15:42:39 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://marketWO.github.io/hugo-start/post/chondromalaciace/</guid>
      <description>Chondromalacie je syndrom patelární bolesti spojený s abnormálním změkčením chrupavky. Tento stav je často výsledkem nedostatečné svalové síly. Patela se stává bolestivou a její chrupavčitá podložka může být změkčena. Tento jev se poměrně často objevuje u dospívajících jedinců a u lidí ve věku do 35 let. Častěji jsou postiženy dívky. Jde o jednu z nejčastějších příčin chronické bolesti kolene.
PATELLA ALTA Pro chondromalacii bývá také typické vyšší postavení čéšky, tzv. patella alta.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All albums of The Beatles</title>
      <link>http://marketWO.github.io/hugo-start/post/another-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://marketWO.github.io/hugo-start/post/another-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is just another post. And it illustrates a mighty functionality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Hugo!</title>
      <link>http://marketWO.github.io/hugo-start/post/welcome-to-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://marketWO.github.io/hugo-start/post/welcome-to-hugo/</guid>
      <description>You’ll find this post in your content/post directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run command hugo server, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.
To add new posts, simply add a file in the content/post directory that follows the convention name-of-post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://marketWO.github.io/hugo-start/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://marketWO.github.io/hugo-start/about/</guid>
      <description>This is a minimal Hugo website created for a course VIKBA07.
Learn more about Hugo with a quick start guide or by exploring its documentation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>